[
  {
    "question": "What company developed and published Valorant?",
    "answer": "riot games"
  },
  {
    "question": "On which date was Valorant officially released for Windows?",
    "answer": "june 2, 2020"
  },
  {
    "question": "What game engine powers Valorant?",
    "answer": "unreal engine 4"
  },
  {
    "question": "What country is the agent Astra from?",
    "answer": "ghana"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the in-game currency called that can be earned by playing games and completing tasks in Valorant?",
    "answer": "kingdom credits"
  },

  {
    "question": "Which agent can create a poison cloud?",
    "answer": "viper"
  },

  {
    "question": "Which agent has a recon bolt?",
    "answer": "sova"
  },

  {
    "question": "Which country is the agent Neon from?",
    "answer": "philippines"
  },

  {
    "question": "What are the characters called in Valorant?",
    "answer": "agents" 
  },
  {
    "question": "What role type is Sage? Duelist, Controller, Sentinel, or Initiator?",
    "answer": "sentinel" 
  },
  {
    "question": "What country is the map Ascent based on?",
    "answer": "italy" 
  },
  {
    "question": "What country is the map Icebox based on?",
    "answer": "russia" 
  },
  {
    "question": "What location is the map Breeze based on?",
    "answer": "bermuda triangle" 
  },
  {
    "question": "What location is the map Fracture based on? Hint: It's a US state.",
    "answer": "new mexico" 
  },
  {
    "question": "What country is the map Lotus based on?",
    "answer": "india" 
  },
  {
    "question": "What country is the map Split based on?",
    "answer": "japan" 
  },
  {
    "question": "Which country is the agent Waylay from?",
    "answer": "thailand"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which agent is from South Korea?",
    "answer": "jett"
  },
  {
    "question":"Which agent has the voiceline 'Nightmare take them!' when they use their ultimate ability?",
    "answer": "fade"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which agent uses a sentry turret?",
    "answer": "killjoy"
  },

  {
    "question": "Which agent was an information broker prior to joining the VALORANT team?",
    "answer": "cypher"
  },

  {
    "question": "True or False: The agent Reyna is considered a Radiant",
    "answer": "true"
  },

  {
    "question": "True or False: The agent KAY/O is considered a Radiant",
    "answer": "true"
  }


]
